Our next conductive this year
is GS.
Good evening everyone. Um I would like
also to join all others in
congratulations victims. So with this
special honor to be inducted in the
international hall of fame.
So it is a very distant
uh honor
and special privilege and great pleasure
to introduce
today who is a friend and also an
exceptional individual of
many. I would like just to highlight a
few titles so that you will understand
what she was able to achieve here.
Included Sana is the founder and chief
executive officer of the local and
global reality company. She's also a
founder and board member of
the Russian
culture. As you have heard also for many
years, she has served as executive
director and board member of the entire
Cleveland cultural organization.
Besides that, she is also a board member
of the Cleveland
B and she is also an executive director
of the
Cleveland Summer Stars
summer music, dance and arts festival.
From this list alone, you can see that
Slana is an individual of many talents,
but I would like to
highlight her one and unique gift.
She has a unique
gift and ability to bring together and
unite people of different cultural
backgrounds, different views and
opinions to work together on common
goals.
This is I believe a very exceptional
talent that she has especially during
this time when world feels so
separated. She also never keeps time.
She stays committed to the goal even
when she is sick or she is feeling that
her ability to complete the task is
maybe
not missing her physical strengths.
So let me also provide you with a brief
information about Slana's background
education so that you can better
understand how she was able to
accomplish
so spent her school years in law school
where she received a formal music
education during her secondary schooling
nurturing her lifelong love of music.
She ran on then to continue her
education at Mos State University, the
number one university in the former
Soviet Union and present day Russia and
that we share. So we where she studied
western philosophy.
After graduation, she went to join an
academic institution, an institute of
psychology and potentially thought that
she will stay as a scientist for the
rest of her life. But this was actually
the history of the Soviet Union when the
so-called was brought into power and the
development. And so during the
story realized that she has a lot of
possibilities and opportunities in front
of her and this is where she started her
first business venture and this was in
1989. 10 years later she came to
Cleveland where she started her new life
and a career in real estate brokerage
and investment. in Cleveland played a
pivotal role in attracting international
investors to Cleveland and promoting the
Cro. She was frequently invited to
Russia in Ukraine as a consultant, a
speaker in real estate conferences where
she also taught master classes. Her
contributions of course extended far
beyond her professional activity. As I
mentioned, she was very actual active in
the
Cleveland community as the vice
president of the Cleveland
cultural. But besides that, SL is a
passion entrepreneur and also investor.
We actually support scientific
innovation particularly in the field of
the research. And this is where we met
some years ago when we started a company
that uses innovative approaches for
concerts
and has been supporting our company
since then and very much interested
in her she was coming along with the
development of the company. So please
join me.
I am so deeply honored and of
course to stand here
tonight. You know the story 7 months
ago. Just
ago, our dear friends and our angel from
the
day,
moment stage
and
I and I sure of what tomorrow will
bring. This simple vision gave me
something to hold on to and that was the
hope that brought me
here. Throughout my life I
was incredibly
fortunate. I was fortunate to be
accepted to the university back in
1981. I was fortunate to experience this
program. Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
I
see and strangely
familiar in the main building of my own
university where I Heat. Heat. Heat.
[Music]
I almost
I see
[Applause]
you.
America, but to me it is one of the most
international places I've ever known.
Our
cultures build rages and nowhere is it
more visible than our human
culture for to be one of three fathers
of they are here Tonight they left the
city but their spirit remains and they
still here supporting the
guards together with our work and
volunteers.
We build and there are in 2018
station
and the war of Russian culture
over fears that are on the stones.
Yeah. Today we
s
Yeah. Heat.
[Music]
Star
War
Yeah. Heat.
or and of course we want to bring this
culture to Cleveland
because
shape
and
natural but all
today's knowledge culture and religion
to this society
All of our volunteers again I I have no
words to not enough words to thank you
for doing what you are doing. Oh my
friends, thank you so
much.
new this year this this 2025 season
it's
international and this year they
competition in
our I feel very proud that we are
bringing down people from not just local
regional and from all over the world to
Cleveland. Introduce Cleveland to this
new audience and it's a great honor to
do
it. Give me a second life.
I'm here because
real
[Music]
soldiers work
for cancer research and they do research
like this And thank you to our
[Music]
beautiful
It shows God to answer. But we
know that there is hope and this hope is
for everybody especially thanks to this
city that we live in and that we
contribute in. And of course I want to
uh give my personal and biggest thank
you to my family to my son who always is
beside me
and my mother is almost years old and
she's here. She could not make it today
unfortunately. But I thank you for your
wisdom and
love. Tonight I stand here filled with
hope for my own journey and for the
future. We are all created
together because the greatest gift we
can offer each other is exactly what I
have received. A reason to believe, a
reason to heal, and a reason to
create. Every story of courage and
contribution deserves to be part of this
hall of fame. Thank you for
Heat up here.